Guide to the Delta Kappa Gamma. Mu Chapter Records 1948-1992
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
Delta Kappa Gamma. Mu Chapter Records
1948-1992
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
Delta Kappa Gamma Society International. Mu Chapter (Bozeman, Mont.)
2472
0.4 linear feet
The Delta Kappa Gamma. Mu Chapter Records consists of materials produced by the organization and its members and include minutes, attendance roles, photos, clippings and a charter.
This collection is open for research.
Charter, meeting minutes, and miscellaneous documents pertaining to the Mu Chapter of Delta Kappa Gamma were donated to Montana State University by a resolution of the membership passed on April 26, 2003 and transferred to the library by chapter president Sue Hamilton.
The Delta Kappa Gamma Society is an organization of women educators, which was founded by Dr. Annie Webb Blanton on May 11, 1929, at the Faculty Women's Club at the University of Texas at Austin. Montana State College estabilished a local Delta Kappa Gamma Society Mu Chapter in the Student Union Building on October 29, 1948. This organization serves as a professional honor society of women educators. Members consist of classroom teachers, professors, administrators, and librarians with three or more years of experience. Selma Apman was elected the Mu Chapter's first President and they have held five meetings per year since 1945.
The Delta Kappa Gamma Society. Mu Chapter records consist of materials produced by the organization and its members and include minutes, attendance roles, photos, clippings, and a charter.
Delta Kappa Gamma Society International-Mu Chapter (Bozeman, Mont.); Delta Kappa Gamma Society-Mu Chapter (Bozeman, Mont.)
Women educators-Montana-Bozeman-Societies, etc
Women; Montana; Bozeman; Photographs
- Meeting minutes, 1948 October - 1950 April (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes, 1950 September - 1952 October (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes, 1952 November - 1954 October (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes, 1954 November - 1956 October (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes, 1956 November - 1958 October (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes, 1958 November - 1960 October (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes, 1960 November - 1962 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes, 1962 November - 1964 October (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes, 1964 October - 1966 April (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes, 1966 August - 1968 August (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes, 1968 November - 1970 April (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes, 1971 March - 1973 August (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes, 1973 October - 1976 January (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes, 1976 February - 1977 November (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes, 1978 January - 1980 April (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes, 1980 October - 1982 November (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Meeting minutes, 1982 October - 1988 September (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Meeting minutes, 1988 October -1992 April (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous documents (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Oversized folder: Mu chapter Charter (Box 1, Folder 20)